I've been longing to see you.
Who the hell is this?!
#5 "Mysterious Cat"
Wh-What's going—
O-Oh, dear... How improper of me.
I'm terribly sorry.
Er, no, it's okay...
This must have happened because
it was all I prayed for, day and night.
The Lord has finally allowed us to meet.
S-So soft...
Er, I mean... Wait! Hold on a
second! Come to your senses!
Who is this?
I don't know her. I have no idea who she is.
Have we met somewhere?
Nah, no way. Nope, nope, nope!
Do you have even the slightest of
feelings for me, Masamune-sama?
She got my name right.
D-Do hot guys
have random girls just hurl themselves
at them before they even know it?
Nah, that can't be.
L-Listen...
I'm pretty sure you've got the wrong person.
Huh?
Milady, it's just about time.
But, Shidou...
It's time.
I am so delighted that I had a chance
to see you, Masamune-sama.
I do hope we will see each other again soon.
Huh?
If you will excuse me.
Hey, wait...
What the hell was that?
Hey, Adagaki-san.
Who was that?
Er, I'm not really sure, either.
Why don't you die?
Milady.
Please do not forget that
you are a Fujinomiya.
You made a promise to your father.
I haven't forgotten.
I believe this will be a most splendid game.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Ma-kun's The Truth Show
There is something that I
really want to say right now!
May the hammer come down
on girls who refuse to listen.
That woman dares to tell me to die
without even hearing me out—yes!
I'm talking about Adagaki Aki!
I am not guilty! I am innocent!
Listen to me, damn it!
Ma'am, I need an egg salad sandwich!
Chicken cutlets! Chicken cutlets!
Ma'am...
I need five yakisoba buns,
four cutlet sandwiches,
and five croquette buns!
All right, this should be more than enough.
She's probably enjoying
her loner feast in that gym
storage room right now.
After all, she is a gluttonous fiend.
No matter how bad her mood might be,
I've brought this many offerings.
Surely she'll at least hear me out.
I-It's okay. It'll work out.
You can't shoot gas guns at people!
Would you have preferred the real thing?
What the hell was that for?
I'm on duty. Aki-sama's orders.
High Voltage
She told me to chase the Pig's
Foot away if he came near.
She's still mad?
Pig's Foot, this didn't seem like
something that she'd let go easily.
What did you do?
Well...
"Well"?
I mean...
"I mean"?
After I talked with you yesterday,
I went to see Adagaki Aki.
She suddenly jumped into your arms?
I swear! I seriously
have no idea who she is!
I don't even know what her name is!
You believe me, right, Master?
M-Master!
To think that you were this hopeless...
Seriously, I'm not!
I told you not to interfere.
You think I'm that resourceful?!
Unresourceful
That's not the point here. Don't you get it?
Is she just going to abandon me?
Fine.
I decided I'd do this myself anyway.
I just have to review what
I'm supposed to say.
You sure went through a lot
yesterday, Adagaki-san.
I went through a lot, too.
But you're my number one girl, Adagaki-san.
No, no!
The wind's so strong.
It is.
Man... I didn't get any sleep at all.
I seriously have no idea who that girl is.
That girl...
Masamune-sama.
But she sure was cute...
Actually, she's pretty much my type.
But I seriously have no idea who she is!
That stupid Cruel Princess pisses me off!
Koiwai Yoshino, too!
What's wrong with Masamune-kun?
No idea. He's been acting pretty suspicious.
We're starting homeroom. Take your seats.
Why am I surrounded by people
who won't listen to me?
I'm going to introduce you
to a new transfer student.
I am Fujinomiya Neko.
I am pleased to make your acquaintance.
Sh-She's beautiful!
So cute!
Fujinomiya-san, go ahead and
take that empty desk over there.
Yes, sir.
All right! I've been waiting
for this five-minute break!
Fujinomiya-san, do you have a moment?
Your hair is so pretty!
What shampoo do you use?
Where did you transfer from?
Wh-What is this?
Seichou Academy.
Seichou?
Oh, I've heard of it. It's an
all-girls boarding school.
I saw it on TV.
It's in the middle of some mountains.
The school looks like a castle.
Wow!
Who cares about all that?!
Just...
let me...
talk to her!
The next class...
That looks good on you!
I'll show you where it is. This way.
Curse you girls!
So that's what it means to feel more
comfortable around the same sex.
It's a violation of the anti-trust act.
The wealth needs to be redistributed.
Hey, Kojuurou. Go mix in with them.
What? No! It's too scary!
It's not scary. They won't
even notice you're there.
Put this bow on. Here.
I need a picture! A picture!
Hurry! Hurry! Wait, hang on!
I'll go.
You will, Makabe-kun?
I just need to talk to her, right?
Th-That's right, Makabe!
That's using your hot-guy-ness!
Makabe-kun, you'd do that for us?
These guys are a real pain.
I'll treat you to Mac!
And karaoke!
I have a ton of things that I want
to ask Fujinomiya Neko myself.
Hey, girls. Do you mind if we join in—
No way!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry for interrupting
your squees and giggles!
Masamune-kun, perfect timing!
Wh-What? What is this?
Masamune-kun, did you know?
Huh?
Fujinomiya-san says she
transferred here just for you.
Huh?
Huh?!
U-Um...
Masamune-sama had no way of knowing.
I personally feel indebted to him, that is all.
Then you should tell him,
right here and now!
Three years ago on Christmas...
Donations
We would deeply appreciate
your warm donations again this Christmas.
Um...
You should dress warmer.
It looked like you were about
to grow wings and fly away.
When you said that to me, Masamune-sama,
you looked like an angel in my eyes.
Wai—
Wait, what's going to happen
to Adagaki-san, then?
Well, this is this, and that's that.
Seriously, wait.
This is like something out of a shojo manga!
Who the hell is that nauseatingly
smug guy supposed to be?!
Three years ago, I was still
a fatty living in Shinshuu!
That's Makabe for you.
Can't be helped if it was Makabe.
They're convinced!
Let's talk for a sec.
Um, Masamune-sama...
If you run so quickly, I'll...
S-Sorry, I didn't notice.
Blood?!
Fujinomiya-san?!
E-Emergency! Emergency!
Where's the medic?!
Wait, should I call 110?
No, it's 119!
But first, the nurse's office...
I'm all right.
I just got dizzy for a moment.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
You dropped some... thing...
Kamego Tomato Ketchup
Mini Pack
That's the blood?
Please do not worry.
I picked a brand that uses the
best natural ingredients.
Er, what's this doing here?
It's a part of a refined lady's tastes.
Tastes?
Think of it as a variation on
a mayonnaise enthusiast.
If not for the situation, I almost
wouldn't want to believe you...
What do you put on your eggs?
Sorry, but I prefer salt and pepper.
Stop trying to change the subject!
More importantly, why would
you tell a lie like that?
I don't know you.
The truth is rather embarrassing.
Huh?
If possible,
I would prefer to keep the truth
a secret between you and me.
Uh, that doesn't explain anything to me...
It doesn't matter to me
that you don't remember.
It doesn't change the fact
that I've always admired you.
Is it a bother to you?
Damn it. She's really cute.
Don't lose your head, Makabe Masamune.
You know this is wrong.
You have to endure.
If you lose your resolve here,
what'll come of your revenge
against that scumball?
I appreciate your feelings, but I'm sorry.
I have someone that I like.
Damn it, I said it. What a waste.
No... That can't be...
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Is she that wonderful?
Actually, she's crude, she's a
glutton, she's unrefined...
She's the opposite of wonderful.
Yeah...
A-Are you two dating?
No. It's one-sided.
I-If it's not a bother,
would you mind telling me who she is?
No, that isn't enough.
I need five K sandwiches,
and five Y sandwiches.
I need another of that
exact same order at 3 PM.
Understood.
That's her, by the window.
The girl with the short hair?
No, the long-haired girl next
to her, with the big attitude...
Oh, I mean in the sense that she's level-headed.
I mean, just going by looks,
the Cruel Princess is unbeatable.
I'm sure Fujinomiya-san will give up.
Ah, she ain't gonna be a problem.
Huh?
Hey, wait a sec!
I apologize for what happened the other day.
You're the girl from...
My name is Fujinomiya Neko.
I truly envy you,
since you have Masamune-sama's affection.
I've gotta stop her!
She's not wearing any?
I'm very mindful when it comes to my health.
Huh?
Feeling moderately tense is
the secret to good health.
Who needs that kind of health tip?!
The trick is in your stride and
how you place your feet.
The trick to what exactly?
I am very blessed.
Regardless of how you might feel about me,
it feels like a miracle that
we're able to speak at all.
Wait, wait, wait...
So annoying.
Crap! I got caught up in the fact
that she's not wearing any!
Leave right now. If you
won't leave, then I will.
Wait!
I want to talk to you about this.
It's not like that!
She's mistaken me for someone else!
That has nothing to do with me!
Are you going to believe her over me?
Huh?
Where do you get off
expecting me to believe you?
I'm telling you to hear me out!
Get away from me! I'll catch
your chronic superficiality!
You guys have some nerve,
boldly skipping class like this.
That unreasonable teacher...
I'm going to dub him
"Mr. Broke-ass from 3-B."
You think you have a right to be mad?
I'm the one who got dragged
into this nonsense.
As punishment, you'll be cleaning
the pool after school!
Endure. I have to endure this.
Well, let's just hurry up and
finish cleaning this pool.
Yes, you're right.
Before I get indiscriminately
assaulted by a certain someone.
I'll start cleaning over there,
so don't you dare come anywhere near me.
What is her problem?! What is her
problem?! What is her problem?!
Ugh, what the hell am
I going to do with you?!
You piss me off... You piss
me off... You piss me off!
M-Makabe!
Sorry, Adagaki-san. That was an accident.
An accident, eh?
The Cruel Princess is sadly
lacking in some areas.
Though she's got some nice legs.
What are you looking at?
Shouldn't you be cleaning?
Yeah, yeah.
Hup...
What the heck? It's so heavy.
Wha—
Makabe, come over here.
This will spill if I walk any further.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm going to accidentally
spill this on you, of course.
That's totally intentional!
Anything "accidental" is way
out of the picture now!
They say, "An eye for an eye,
and a tooth for a tooth," right?
Aren't you thinking of
repaying a debt twofold?
It's accidental!
No accident is that vindictive!
There's no way I'll be the only one to get wet.
Come on, give me a break.
I'm not wearing a swimsuit.
So?
You want me to go home
in drenched underwear?
Maybe you shouldn't wear any, then.
You two can go commando together.
She's hopeless. I need to do something, fast.
Come, now. Be grateful for this water
that I'm going to accidentally...
Serves you right.
Is she drowning? Could it
be that she can't swim?
Wait, I thought she was good at sports!
I'll be right there!
Just a bit more...
I guess her feet touched the bottom.
I thought you didn't want to get wet.
I can't help it. My body moved on its own.
I can't have you dying on me,
for various reasons.
Huh... I see.
So it just moved on its own.
I figured it was no more than that.
Then what do you want me to say?!
If I said it's because I like you,
you wouldn't believe me anyway!
Wha— I never said anything like that!
You might as well have!
It's true that I wanted to save you.
Sorry for overstepping my bounds.
There's no getting through to someone
who's closed off to begin with.
That's what sucks about it being one-way.
I don't get it. Why am I so annoyed by this?
I just...
Then prove it to me.
Prove it?
Yes. Prove that you like me.
You can't?
What would it take for you to believe me?
Well, for example...
You could kiss me.